Maltese, Serphin R.; Papers apap382
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Serphin R. Maltese Papers
1935-2021
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
apap382
31.2 cubic ft.
The Serphin R. Maltese Papers document his career as a State Senator in the New York's 15th Senate District and his pre- and post-Senate service.
Content Description
This collection contains correspondence, programs, news clips, community event materials, media releases/communications materials, subject files, constiuent case materials, and a small selection of DVDs and video tapes. The majority of the materials document Senator Serphin R. Maltese's service in the New York State Senate, although some of the materials are from his pre- and post-Senate life. To review the Senator's work as Chairman of the New York State Conservative Party, see collection apap060, Conservative Party of New York State Records.
Arrangement of Collection
The collection is organized into four series (Series 1: Pre-Senate Career, Series 2: Senate Subject Files, Series 3: Constituent Case Files, Series 4: Post-Senate Career). Series 1, 2, and 4 are arranged chronologically and Series 3 is arranged alphabetically by last name.
Biographical Note
Born in Corona, Queens in 1932, Serphin R. Maltese was first elected to the New York State Senate in November 1988 on the Republican, Conservative, and Right to Life Party lines. He was re-elected for 10 terms on the Republican, Conservative, and Independence Party lines. In 2008, he lost his bid for re-election and retired from elective office. He represented the 15th Senatorial District in Queens serving 320,000 constituents.
Maltese graduated from Stuyvesant High School, served in the Marine Corps Reserves, and then served in the Army 45th Infantry Division during the Korean War. After his military service, he went to Manhattan College, on an awarded Regents Scholarship and the G.I. Bill, and received a BA degree. Maltese was awarded a war service scholarship to Fordham Law School where he received his LLB and JD degrees. He was admitted to the New York State Bar in 1963 and admitted to practice before the U.S. Supreme Court.
Maltese and his wife Constance were co-founders of the New York State Conservative Party in 1962. Maltese became executive director of the New York State Conservative Party in 1971 and Chairman of the Queens Conservative Party in 1972. He was elected to the position of state chairman of the party in 1986, a position in which he served until his election as Senator, when he voluntarily relinquished that post.
Prior to his election to the State Senate, Maltese served as a Queens assistant district attorney and deputy chief of the Homicide Bureau.
In 1965, Maltese initially ran for election; an unsuccessful State Senate bid on William F. Buckley, Jr.'s mayoral ticket. In 1969, Maltese was a citywide coordinator for Senator John Marchi's mayoral bid and in 1970 he became law chairman and election law advisor to U.S. Senator James L. Buckley in his successful third party victory on the Conservative-Independent Alliance party lines. He then served as counsel to Senator Buckley and then as counsel to U.S. Senator Alfonse D'Amato. Maltese also served as counsel to Assemblywoman Rosemary Gunning. Maltese was elected a New York State Reagan-Bush elector in the 1980 and 1984 presidential elections. He also served as New York State Chairman of Conservatives for Ronald Reagan in 1980. He served for seven years as a member of Senator D'Amato's Federal Judicial Selection Panel. He served for more than 25 years on the National Board of Directors of the American Conservative Union.
Following Maltese's election to the State Senate in 1988, he served in a number of leadership positions. He served as chairman of the Veterans Committee; chairman of the Consumer Protection Committee; chairman of the Committee on Crime Victims, Crime and Correction; chairman of the Elections Committee; chairman of the Committee on Arts and Cultural Affairs; and chairman of the Cities Committee. In 2006, he was the only Senate Majority member from New York City on the Higher Education Committee. He also served in the Senate Leadership as vice chairman of the Majority Conference.
As a leader for governmental reform and disclosure, upon his election in November 1988, Maltese voluntarily gave up the practice of law to serve as a full time Senator. He practiced only "pro bono" and never accepted a referral, commission or fee of any kind during his 20 years in the Senate.
Maltese has been active in and honored by many community organizations. Of particular note, he has been honored by the New York State Department of Labor with the "We Will Always Remember" award for honoring the memory of the 146 immigrant victims of the Triangle Shirtwaist Factory Fire of March 25, 1911 where his grandmother and two aunts perished. Maltese serves as president of the Triangle Fire Memorial Association.
Serphin Maltese and the former Constance Mary DelVecchio were married for 63 years at the time of her passing away in 2018. They had two daughters and four grandchildren.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Serphin Maltese donated materials in this collection to the M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives in November 2019, September 2020, November 2021, and September 2022.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Separated Materials
The archivist transferred one monograph: New American Woman by Constance DelVecchio Maltese to the book division of Special Collections. It will be catalogued and included in the University Library Catalog.
Maltese, Serphin R.; Politics and Politicians; Queens County (N.Y.)--Politics and government; Conservative Party of New York State; Republican Party (N.Y.)
- Pre-Senate Files, 1935-1988; 1; 3.5 cubic ft.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  The Pre-Senate series contains Serphin Maltese's activities prior to becoming the State Senator for the 15th district. This includes his work as Queen's Assistant District Attorney, his efforts as co-founder of the New York State Conservative Party, his 1976 campaign for assembly member in Queen's 37th District, his work on campaigns for several high profile Conservative and Republican candidates and his campaigns for State Senate in 1984 and 1988. The types of records in this series include correspondence, campaign materials, clippings, administrative files, photographs, and newsletters.
  - Women's Republican Association of Woodhaven, 1935-1937 (Oversize 1, Folder 1)
  - Maltese Bio, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Manhattan College - Officers of the Society, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ridgewood Post No. 123 Bylaws, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dewey, Thomas, Press, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Goldwater, Barry, Campaign Materials, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Queens Borough Lodge No. 878, 1964-1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Conservative Club Correspondence, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - General Subject Files, 1965-1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - New York State Bar Association Literature, 1965-1973 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Queens District Attorney Bulletins, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Queens Legislative District Map, 1966 (Oversize 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - ELM-JACK Post No. 298, 1966; 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Neighbors United to Save Our Schools Inc., 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Alpha Phi Delta, 1966-1968 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Queens District Attorney General, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Queens County Catholic Lawyers Guild, 1966-1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Drug Use/Crime Prevention, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Fordham Law Alumni Association, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Homicide in Queens - Office of the DA, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - New York State Conservative Party, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Queens County Salute to Our Armed Forces, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Alexander Hamilton Conservative Club/We Care, 1967; 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Assistant District Attorney, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars, 1967-1968; Undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Juniper Park Civic Association, 1967-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Parents and Taxpayers of Ridgewood - Glendale Maspeth - Middle Village, 1967-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District Attorneys Associations, 1967-1977; 1987 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Buckley Campaign, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Conservative Club Letters and Ephemera, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Crimmins, Alice, Murder Trial - Asst. District Attorney, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Queens District Attorney: Prisoner Transport, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Wallace for President, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Crime Prevention Plays, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Queens Membership Organizations, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Queens County Bar Association, 1968-1974 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - American Judicature Society, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Attorney General John Mitchell Press Releases, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - March Mayoral Campaign, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Our Lady of Hope Rectory Parish Council, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Queens Conservative Organization Letters, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Queens News Clippings, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Ridgewood Post No. 123 Newsletters, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Temporary State Commission to Study the Cause of Campus Unrest, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Cross - Endorsement Policy Memoranda and Press, 1969; 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Rosemary R. Gunning Flyers and Newsletters, 1969-1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Clippings, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Cody, Arlene, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Community Events, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Conservative Candidate Election Press Materials, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Democratic Candidate Flyers, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Independent Alliance Party Certificate, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Maltese, Serphin and Constance - Photograph, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Newsletters, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Survey of School for the Deaf, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1970; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Criminal Procedure Law - St. John's Law Review, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Correspondence, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - New York State Legislature, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Queens District Attorney Press Release, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Triangle Fire Press, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Queens Organization Flyers and Mailers, 1971; Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Court Reform Memos and Clippings, 1971-1976 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Ashbrook Campaign, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - New York State Conservative Party, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Party Enrollment: Rosaro et. al. vs. New York, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Queens News Clippings, 1972; 1974 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Political Newspapers, 1972; 1982 (Oversize 1, Folder 3)
  - Community Events, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Maltese News Clippings, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Biaggi, Mario - Press, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Congressional Record, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Fuchsberg, Jacob - Chief Judge Petition, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Presidential Inauguration Ephemera, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - The Eagle of the 33rd Assembly District, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Impeachment Pamphlet, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - State of Board of Elections: Election Results, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Catholic Voting Concern, 1974; Undated (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Community Events, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Queens College Speech and Hearing Center, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Court Case Documents, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Elmhurst Hospital Center, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Hugh's Sorry Now - New York State Legislative Correspondents' Association, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - "NYC Facts", 1975 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Newsletters, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Catholic War Veterans, 1975; 1988; Undated (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - City Club of New York, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Fire Protection in Richmond Hill: Press, Studies, Petitions, 1975-1978 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Assembly Campaign, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - League of Women Voters: Legislative News, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Republican National Convention, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Rhodes, John, Campaign, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - We Care Membership Flyers, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Directory of Members of New York State Legislature and Congress, 1976; 1982 (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Community Events, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Criminal Law Legislation, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Empire State Report: The Future of the Republican Party, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Marijuana Bill, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Perez, Raoul, Dedication, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Right to Life Committee, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Swidorski Dissertation Acknowledgements, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Triangle Fire Press, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Farber, Barry, Campaign, 1977; Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Queens News Clippings, 1977-1978 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Death Penalty Documents, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - DelliBovi Congressional Campaign, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Duryea Campaign, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ferraro ZIP Codes, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - History of Italian American Discrimination at CUNY, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Republican Committee Events, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Inner Circle Presents, 1978; 1980 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Clippings, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Lehrman Campaign Press, 1978-1982 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Direct Mailers and Pamphlets, 1978-1979; Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Alpha Phi Delta Newsletters, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Community Events, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Fordham Law Reunion, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - New York State Representative Guidebook, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Newsletters, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Notary Public Application, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Queens County Republican Committee, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Scotto, Anthony, Memorandum, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - New York State Assembly Phone Book, 1979-1980 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Bang - Jensen, Lisa - National Review, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Board of Elections Results and Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Boy Scouts Newsday Insert, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - D'Amato CBS Interview, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - D'Amato Campaign, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - "Election Argument Settler", 1980 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Election News Clippings and Flyers, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Electoral College, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - IL Progresso - D'Amato Headline, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Legislative Commission on Economy and Efficiency in Government, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Reagan Pamphlets, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Republican Committees, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Triangle Fire Press, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Young Americans For Freedom, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Empire State Report, 1980-1981; 1984 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Clippings, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Commission on Judicial Nominations, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Esposito Campaign Press, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Fordham Dean - Possible Replacement Letter, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Inauguration Ephemera, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Koch Endorsements, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - New York State Republican Party, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Christ the King Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Queens Enrollment Books - Conservative Party, 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Judicial Screening Committee, 1981-1983; 1988 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Koch, Ed - Press, 1981-1983; 1986 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Rusk, Brian and Pulaski Association, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Coalition for Lesbian and Gay Rights Survey, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Election Results, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Emery, Jim - Assembly Member, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Gubernatorial Vote Analysis, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - New York Republican State Committee Annual Dinner, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Queens County Conservative Party, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Republican Candidate News Clippings, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Christmas Party Invitations, 1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Prayer in Schools, 1982; Undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Correspondence, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Queens Citizens Organization, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - D'Amato Subject Files, 1982-1984; Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Knorr - Santucci, 1982-1984; 1988; Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Pro Life Documents, 1982-1986 (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Von Raab, William - Commissioner of Customs, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Committee to Make New York #1 Again, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - "The Day After", 1983 (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Fink Plan Press Clippings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Fort Totten, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Maltese Press Clippings, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Queens County Republican Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Reaganomics/Citizens for Reagan, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Republican National Committee Fundraising Acts, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Ridgewood Property Owners, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - United States Attorney Federal Judicial Committee, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - White House Digest, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Community Events, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Juniper Park Civic Association, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 89)
  - Padavan, Senator Frank, 1983-1984; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
  - 37th Assembly District Clippings, 1983-1988 (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - D'Amato, Alfonse Press and Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - Archbishop O'Connor Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 93)
  - Bush vs. Ferraro News Clippings, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 94)
  - Christ the King, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Congressional Campaign: Asian-American Support, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 96)
  - Congressional Campaign: Campaign Overview, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 97)
  - Congressional Campaign: Debate Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 98)
  - Congressional Campaign: Debate Press, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 99)
  - Congressional Campaign: Designating Petition, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 100)
  - Congressional Campaign: Donor Response Letters, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 101)
  - Congressional Campaign: Election Press, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 102)
  - Congressional Campaign: Flyers and Mailers, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 103)
  - Congressional Campaign: General File, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 104)
  - Congressional Campaign: Letters of Support/Endorsements, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 105)
  - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 106)
  - Democratic Primary Candidates, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 107)
  - Designating Petitions, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Duane, John Campaign Materials, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - Election Results, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 110)
  - Emery, Jill - Congressional Campaign, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Gun Organization, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Italian Americans for Better Government, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Marshall, Dr. Robert S. - Correspondence and Clippings, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - MTA Press Clippings, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Post-Election Appeal, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Queens Polling Places, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Reagan-Bush Campaign Materials, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Reagan-Bush Poster - New York Republican State Committee, 1984 (Oversize 1, Folder 4)
  - Republican County Committee Lincoln Day, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Right to Life Questionnaire, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - State Executive Committee Meeting, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Successful Candidate's Guide to Winning Women's Votes, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Urban Homestead Act, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Knorr, Martin, Subject Files, 1984; 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - American of Italian Heritage Inc., 1984-1988 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Crime Victims Board Annual Report, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Imperiale, John, Assembly Campaign, 1984-1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - D'Amato Campaign, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Manton, Thomas, Campaign Materials, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Board of Elections - Agenda for Reform, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Citizens for Appropriate Punishment (CAP), 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Citizens for the Republic, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Clippings, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Coal Burning Legislation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Christ the King Hall of Fame, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - "Cuomo vs. Archbishop O'Connor", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Friends of Maltese Receipts and Disbursements, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Greater Ridgewood Restoration Corporation, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Inauguration Materials, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Italian Americans Organizations, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Judge Defeis Nomination, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Linhardt - "Courting the Jewish Vote", 1985 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Mentally Ill - Homeless Report, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Newsletters, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Pamphlets and Flyers, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Wars on Drugs, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Women's Republican Club of Queens County, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - New York State Republican Committee Publications, 1985; Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Christ the King, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Community Events, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Queens Borough Magazine, 1985-1986; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Queens News Clippings, 1985-1986; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Goetz, Bernhard, 1985-1988 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Right to Life Party, 1985-1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Admissions and Bar Recommendations, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Archdiocese of New York, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Board of Elections, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Bush, George H.W. - Dinner Plans, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Bush, Vice President - Remarks, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Calandra, John and Joan, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Catholic Public Policy Coalition, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - CAUSA International, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Clippings, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Conservative State Committee List, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Correspondence, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Crime Victims Board Report, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Gay and Position Bill, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Guile, Norman for Assembly, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Hirschfeld News Clippings, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Legislative Correspondence Association, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Monday Club, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Morality in Media, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - New York State Legislative Commission on Public-Private Cooperation, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - New York State Senate Republican Campaign Committee, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Pearson, Ronald - South African Embassy, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Perciaccante, Marianne - History of NYSCP paper, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Professional Discipline Process Update, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Republican Candidate for New York Elections, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Republican Candidate Press, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Vietnam Veterans of America - Queens Chapter, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Visits International for Soviets and Americans (VISA), 1986 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - WPIX Editorials, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Anderson, Senator Warren, 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - "Changing Faces", 1986-1987 (Box 3, Folder 76)